<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Adventure In Tandem</title>
    <link>https://adventureintandem.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Adventure In Tandem</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019 15:02:17 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://adventureintandem.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Tour Map</title>
      <link>https://adventureintandem.com/tourmap/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019 15:02:17 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adventureintandem.com/tourmap/</guid>
      <description>Below you will find a map and table of all of our rides so far on our 2019 tour from Bangkok, Thailand to Barcelona, Spain. Check back often to follow along.
You can also follow along the rides on Strava, which also happens to be where this map is being built from. We&amp;rsquo;re sorry but test doesn&amp;rsquo;t work properly without JavaScript enabled. Please enable it to continue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Bike Friday Touring Tandem</title>
      <link>https://adventureintandem.com/touring-tandem/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 15:16:46 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adventureintandem.com/touring-tandem/</guid>
      <description>The choice of touring bicycle can really make or break your bike tour. If you have one that is a pain to work on and move around, or have one that just doesn&amp;rsquo;t work very well the tour becomes a trial of your mechanic skills.
On the other hand, if you have a bike that works great and is reliable you are setup for success on your tour.
For that reason and many more we will detail below we bought a Bike Friday Tandem Twosday to tour on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Us</title>
      <link>https://adventureintandem.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jan 2019 10:18:02 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adventureintandem.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>Have any questions about how to bike tour?
Wondering what you need to do to make a long-term bike tour happen for yourself?
Feel free to reach out and we will answer all of your questions.
Justin and Cara
Your Name Email Address An email address is required.  Message   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019 Route</title>
      <link>https://adventureintandem.com/route/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2019 17:24:30 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adventureintandem.com/route/</guid>
      <description>2019 is the year of the bike tour for us. Justin has semi-retired from work to allow us to travel the world for a year or 2, or really however long we want to tour the world.
The plan for this first year is to follow in the footsteps of many of the wonderful Warmshowers guests that we have had stay with us in Zhuhai, China over the past 4 years.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>